Register of the Milton Friedman papers 77011.4088897
Hoover Institution Archives
- Audio-Visual File, 1969-1988 (Boxes 102-107)
  - Sound recordings of speeches, interviews, conversation transcripts, and dictation, 1961-1988; 19.0 Cassettes
    - "Economics of Health Care,", 1977 March (Box 102)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004913
    - Courtroom dedication address at USD School of Law, 1977 November 7 (Box 102)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004916
    - Meet the Press, WRC Radio, 1978 November 12 (Box 102)
      This interview concerns the current "tax revolt." Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004919
    - Wall Street Week: "Happy New Year - Part One" (program 927), 1980 January 4 (Box 102)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004920
      Friedman is the special guest.
    - American Focus radio program featuring Milton Friedman, circa 1982-1984 (Box 102)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004945
    - "The Real Threat to U.S. Security," Commonwealth Club of California, San Francisco, 1983 April 15 (Box 102)
      Friedman believes the welfare state is the greatest threat to the United States' security, not the Soviet Union. He begins by recalling British humorist Parkin's second law that expenditure rises to meet income. After analyzing the differences in defense spending versus total spending in the 1950s and the 1980s, he notes that non-defense spending is rising out of control. He tells the audience that a Republican-controlled committee in Congress cut President Reagan's defense spending and increased non-defense spending. For solutions, Friedman calls for a constitutional amendment to limit total spending, and to limit the role of government. He believes there is no area where the government is not funding both sides of an issue (i.e. tariffs for one foreign good and subsidies for another foreign good).
      The question-and-answer session touches on Social Security, the national debt, the Federal Reserve (of which he is very critical), Chile, and the separation of economists into schools. Friedman does not believe the debt is a problem; he is more concerned with future financial obligations.
    - "The Economy: Where Are We Headed?," Commonwealth Club of California, San Francisco, 1984 July 27 (Box 102)
    - "Is Hyperinflation Inevitable?," Commonwealth Club of California, San Francisco, 1985 June 28 (Box 102)
      Friedman speaks about the effect of the new world monetary structure, where a commodity backs no currency. He recites the history of currencies, both commodity-based and fiat, in various countries, noting the dollar went off the gold standard first in 1914 though only formalized in 1971. He then looks at Fisher's thesis that currencies always return to a commodity base after experimenting with paper money. Friedman disagrees with Fisher. He explains that inflation is used to decrease the national debt's percentage of GDP. However, he says countries generally take actions to bring down inflation once it becomes prominent because inflation is politically unpopular. Friedman ends for calling for an institutional and constitutional rule for monetary policy in America, but asks to not be misunderstood as calling for a return to the gold standard.
      Additional topics covered during the question-and-answer session include wave analysis, the trade and budget deficits, how to balance a budget, the International Monetary Fund especially its activities after the breakdown of Bretton Woods as a world central bank, Argentina, OPEC, corporate taxes, Fed rate non-predictions, and Friedman's distaste for a political appointment.
    - Portfolio of State Issues, volume 5 number 2, circa 1988 (Box 102)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004946
      Included is William F. Buckley Jr. interviewing Milton Friedman on recession.
  - Economics Cassette Series sound recordings, 1968-1978; 207.0 Cassettes (Boxes 103-107)
    Boxes 103-107 CLOSED. Use the provided copy reference numbers to listen to recordings in the Archives reading room or click the links to listen to them online.
    The Economics Cassette Series was a bi-weekly, subscription-based series that ran from 1968 to 1978. Instructional Dynamics Incorporated (IDI) produced the series, which served as something of a companion to Friedman's Newsweek columns of the same era. There are 215 total cassettes in the series. As a general rule, every cassette features the same program on both sides. Each program is an interview with Milton Friedman, recorded either in Chicago, Illinois or in Vermont. The Chicago programs were recorded at the Friedman residence with William Clark of the Chicago Tribune conducting the interviews. Dr. Friedman's wife, Rose, conducted the interviews in the Vermont recordings. An exception to the above is a guest appearance by Paul A. Samuelson.
    - 1. Untitled, 1968 November; 21:36 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004950
    - 2. "The Presidential Election and Its Effects on the Economy,", 1968 November; 26:16 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004951
    - 3. Untitled, 1968 November; 24:55 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004952
    - 4. Untitled, 1968; 23:08 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004953
    - 5. "Exchange Rates, Fixed and Varying,", undated; 27:08 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004954
    - 6. "Paul McCracken and the Council of Economic Advisers, Inflation, the Minimum Wage, and Unemployment,", undated; 25:53 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004955
    - 7. "Unemployment, the Federal Reserve and Inflation, Wages, Labor Unions, and George Shultz,", 1968 December; 28:33 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004956
    - 8. "Currency Recycling, Crawling Pegs, Hyperinflation, and the Economic Policy of the Nixon Administration and the Federal Reserve Board,", 1968 December; 29:31 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004957
    - 9. "New Administration Policies, Surtax Possibilities,", 1969 January; 25:06 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004958
    - 10. "Decrease in Growth Rate of Monetary Supply,", 1969 January; 27:07 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004959
    - 11. "The 10 Percent Surtax, the 1969 Economic Report, and Is a New Crisis Coming?,", 26:00 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004961
    - 12. "Exchange Rates and Imports, Monetary Versus Fiscal Policy, and Measures of Monetary Policy,", 1969; 27:27 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004963
      William Clark joins the series for his first appearance and interviews Milton Friedman.
    - 13. "Second Half of 1969, Slowdown Foreseen, Money/Cause or Effect,", 28:21 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004964
    - 14. "New Bretton Woods Would be Disaster, Monetary Policy Article in New York Times,", undated; 24:00 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004968
    - 15. "Conglomerates, Tax Reform,", undated; 24:38 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004969
    - 16. "Divergent Monetary Trends,", undated; 28:06 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004970
      Friedman discusses M1 and M2.
    - 17. "British Bank Rate, French Revolution,", undated; 29:03 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004971
    - 18. "Current Monetary News, Conservative Disappointment with Nixon, Independence of Federal Reserve,", undated; 25:35 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004974
    - 19. "Monetary Developments, Demand and Supply of Money and Credits, Inflation and Unemployment,", undated; 26:57 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004978
    - 20. "Current Monetary and Economic Developments,", undated; 28:48 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004986
    - 21. "International Financial Picture, Reduction of United States Exchange Controls, Credit Restraint Euro-Dollars,", undated; 29:47 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004987
    - 22. "Current Monetary Developments, Prospects for Interest Rates, Nixon Budget, Peace Rumors and the Market Federal, Funds Rate,", undated; 31:07 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004988
    - 23. "Nixon's Tax Proposals,", undated; 29:55 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004993
    - 24. "Reaction to Samuelson, Impact of De Gaulle's Resignation, Effect on U. S. Dollar,", 1969; 28:06 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0004999
    - 25. "Monetary Policy, Gold Prices, Vietnam Peace, Investment Tax Credit, Collectivism,", undated; 27:59 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005002
    - 26. "Current Monetary Indication, Balance of Payments Deficit, Rush for German Marks,", undated; 28:50 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005004
    - 27. "Businessmen and Inflation, Bond Market, Harry Schultz Letter,", undated; 27:24 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005009
    - 28. "Money Supply, Pressure for Rate Increase, David Kennedy and Wage and Price Controls,", undated; Part 1, 29:39; Part 2, 14:28 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005274
      This recording also includes dictation about a trip to Israel.
    - 29. "Current Conditions, A.B.A. International Monetary Conference,", undated; 26:17 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005012
    - 30. "Monetary Developments, Interest Rates, Compensating Balances and Interest on Demand Deposits,", 1969 July 10; 21:57 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005284
    - 31. "Quantity of Money, Behavior of Interest Rates, Real vs. Nominal Interest Rates,", 1969 July 24; 22:48 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005285
    - 32. "Monetary Developments, Future Federal Policy Lag in Effect of Money, Tax Legislation,", 1969 August 7; 26:24 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005290
    - 33. "Nixon Welfare Proposal, Revision of Money Supply Figures Subscribers' Questions,", 1969 August 21; 28:21 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005294
    - 34. "Japan, Current Economic Conditions, Overkill, Interest Deduction, Capital Gains, Rediscounting,", 1969 September 4; 28:58 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005298
    - 35. "Unemployment Figures Monetary Developments, Interest Rates, Economic Forecast,", 1969 October 8; 28:04 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005299
    - 36. "Appointment of Arthur Burns to Fed, German Mark and Exchange Rates,", undated; 29:19 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005305
    - 37. "Monetary Developments, Economic Development, Cost of Anti-Inflation [?], Attacking Inflation [?], Production/Property Taxes,", undated; 28:45 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005311
    - 38. "Monetary Developments, Interest Rates, Rinfret's Predictions, Stock Market, Bank Holdings Co. Comm. Paper,", 1969 November 19; 28:23 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005312
    - 39. "1970 Forecast,", 1969 December; Part 1, 28:14; Part 2, 28:17 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005315
      Milton Friedman and Paul Samuelson give economic forecasts for 1970 (Friedman part 1, Samuelson part 2).
    - 40. "Monetary Developments, Feasibility of Steady Monetary Growth, Rinfret's Predictions,", 1969 December 17; 27:30 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005321
    - 41. "Prospective Money Situation, Velocity Behavior,", 1969 December 31; 27:20 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005322
    - 42. "Nixon Reaction to Recession, Wage Settlements and Unemployment,", 1970 January 15; 27:36 (Box 103)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005327
    - 43. "Money Stock, Regulation Question, Pollution,", undated; 28:21 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005433
    - 44. "Bond Market Turn, Debt, Bankruptcies,", 1970 February 12; 27:20 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005434
    - 46. "Economic and Monetary Conditions,", undated; 25:22 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005436
    - 47. "Japan and Korea, Monetary Developments, Economic Developments,", 1970 April 2; 27:54 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005437
    - 48. "Income Tax, Economic Models, Canada vs. U.S. in Cost Depression, Pollution,", 1970 April 15; 28:20 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005439
    - 49. "General Economic Conditions, Market Price Increases, Margin Requirements on Stocks, Liquidity Crisis,", 1970 April 29; 28:07 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005440
    - 50. "Stock Market, Is This 1929?, Low Point of Current Revision, Subscribers Questions,", 1970 May 16; 32:48 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0002063
    - 51. "Stock Market, Credit Crisis, Monetary Policy, Income Policy,", 1970 May 27; 27:17 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0002066
    - 52. "Distinctive Features of Recession, High Interests Rates, Control of Money Supply,", 1970 June 10; 28:03 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005441
    - 53. "Penn Central Bankruptcy, Monetary Development, President Nixon's Economic Sale, Subscribers' Questions,", 1970 June 24; 28:30 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005443
    - 54. "Monetary Developments, Interest Rates/Money Supply, British Tax Policy, Debt Liquidation/Dollar Devaluation/Black Angus,", 1970 July 8; 27:39 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005445
    - 55. "Inflation, Bottoming of Economy, Interest Rates, Capital Spending,", 1970 July 22; 26:56 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005599
    - 56. "Monetary Developments, Bottoming Of Recession, Long Term Interest Rates, Recommended Money Supply, Real Money Supply, Jewish Conspiracy,", 1970 August 6; 29:28 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005600
    - 57. "General Review of Outlook for Money, Business, Inflation, Stock Market, Interest Rates,", 1970 August 20; 28:13 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005601
    - 59. "Current Economic Condition,", 1970 October 15; 28:16 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005602
    - 60. "Pre-Election Economic Perspective, Real Money Supply, Residual Money Supply,", 1970 November 4; 27:54 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005603
    - 61. "Industrial Production Decline, Monetary Development, Fed Policy, Subscribers' Questions,", 1970 November 18; 21:30 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005604
    - 62. "Monetary Figure Revisions, Spending,", 1970 December 3; 19:34 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005605
    - 63. "Outlook for 1971,", 1970 December 16; 29:26 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005606
    - 64. "Economic Development, Constructive Money, Growth,", 1970 December 31; 27:23 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005607
    - 65. "Monetary Developments, Depreciation Liberalization, Steel Prices,", 1971; 21:08 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005608
    - 66. "Monetary Figures, Steel Prices Ploy, State of Union Message,", 1971 January 27; 20:58 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005609
    - 67. "Administration Projections, Projected Default,", 1971 February 10; 20:05 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005610
    - 68. "Davis Bacon Act, Forecasts, Band Market, Common Market Currency,", 1971 February 24; 24:00 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005611
    - 69. "Monetary Development, Bond Market, Budget, Escalated Bond,", 1971 March 12; 23:05 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005612
    - 70. "S.S.T., Oil Import Quotas, Interest Rates,", 1971 March 29; 24:41 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005613
    - 71. "Monetary Developments, Living with Inflation,", 1971 April 7; 23:26 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005614
    - 72. "Monetary Development, Stock Market, GNP Growth, National Dividend Plan,", 1971 April 21; 24:23 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005616
    - 73. "International Monetary Crises,", 1971 May 10; 25:31 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005617
    - 74. "International Monetary Developments, Domestic Recovery,", 1971 May 20; 25:08 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005618
    - 75. "Interest Rates and Money, Subscribers Questions,", 1971 June 2; 25:25 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005619
    - 76. "Time's Board of Economists, St. Louis Price Predictions, Cost-Push-Inflation,", 1971 June 15; 28:47 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005620
    - 77. "Monetary Development, Nixon Game Plan, Unemployment, Exchange Control,", 1971 July 1; 29:58 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005621
    - 78. "Mr. Nixon's Policy, Unemployment, Effect of Monetary Changes, Inflation Potential,", 1971 July 14; 30:57 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005622
    - 79. "Monetary Development, Monetarist Forecasts, Seasonal Adjustment of Money, Balance of Payment,", 1971 July 27; 28:37 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005723
    - 80. "Unilateral Devaluation of Dollar, Speculation for the Yen Inflation,", 1971 August 11; 25:41 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005726
    - 81. "The President's New Economic Policy,", circa 1971; 30:12 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005727
    - 82. "International Monetary Development, Domestic Economy,", 1971 September 27; 29:33 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005730
    - 83. "Domestic Economic Conditions,", 1971 October 6; 29:57 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005732
    - 84. "Monetary Development, Subscribers' Questions,", 1971 October 20; 33:35 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005735
    - 85. "Slow Down in Economic Expansion, Prospect for Renewed Recession,", 1971 November 4; 30:47 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005738
    - 86. "Money Developments, Pay and Price Board, Subscribers' Questions,", 1971 November 20; 31:40 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005739
    - 87. "Forecast for 1972,", 1971 December 1; 31:20 (Box 104)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005740
    - 88. "Dollar Devaluation-Money Supply,", 1971 December 15; 29:38 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005754
    - 89. "Have Monetary Policies Failed?, Monetary and International Developments,", 1971 December 26; 27:42 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005755
    - 91. "Deficits, GNP Estimates, Money, Subscribers' Questions,", 1972 January 26; 28:50 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005758
    - 92. "Monetary Policy, Fiscal Policy, Subscribers' Questions,", 1972 February 9; 27:50 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005759
    - 93. "Current Monetary Conditions, Value Added Tax, Subscribers' Questions,", 1972 February 23; 28:02 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005762
    - 94. "Monetary Development, International Monetary Changes, Linked Bonds,", 1972 March 8; 30:31 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005765
    - 95. "Money, Economy, Pay Board, British Tax Cut, Drugs,", 1972 March 22; 29:15 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005766
    - 96. "The Fed, And Inflation, Effects of Controls, Book by Meigs, Hawaii,", 1972 April 5; 29:58 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005767
    - 97. "State of the Economy, Effect of Controls, Interest Rates, Prospects for the Future,", 1972 May 3; 27:35 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005768
    - 98. "Hong Kong and Japan Economics,", 1972 April 25; 30:16 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005769
    - 99. "Monetary Growth, Federal Reserve Emphasis on Reserves, Business and Inflation Outlook,", 1972 May 17; 27:06 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005774
    - 100. "Moscow Summit, Shultz Appointment, International Monetary Conference,", 1972 May 31; 27:42 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005775
    - 101. "Monetary Developments, Money in Stock Market, Reducing Government,", 1972 June 14; 27:41 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005776
    - 104. "Economic Reports, International Monetary Crisis,", 1972 July 26; 31:15 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005777
    - 106. "Monetary Developments, Inflation, Kondratieff Cycle,", 1972 August 24; 28:37 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005778
    - 107. "European Fear of Inflation, U.S. Monetary Developments, Flood Relief, Gold,", 1972 September 20; 29:15 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005779
    - 108. "International Monetary Fund,", 1972 October 5; 25:16 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005780
    - 109. "Government Spending,", 1972 October 18; 25:16 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005781
    - 110. "Monetary Development, Personal Income Projections, Interest Rate Control, Canadian Economy,", 1972 November 1; 23:22 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005782
    - 111. "Election, Dow Breaking 1,000, Balance of Payments, British Freeze, Industrial Products,", 1972 November 17; 24:36 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005783
    - 112. "Economic Outlook for 1973,", 1972 November 29; 24:13 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005784
    - 113. "Medical Economics, Monetary Developments, Price Controls, Fiscal Policy,", 1973 January 17; 28:37 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005785
    - 114. "Budget Message, Economic Report, International,", 1973 January 31; 29:06 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005786
    - 115. "International Crisis, Monetary Developments, Governor Reagan's Tax Limitations Proposal,", 1973 February 14; 29:28 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005787
    - 116. "International Monetary Crisis, Domestic Monetary Growth,", 1973 March 5; 24:44 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005788
    - 117. "Yugoslavia, International Monetary Development,", 1973 March 14; 27:10 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005789
    - 118. "Report on Yugoslavia and Italy,", 1973 April 13; 28:01 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005790
    - 119. "Inflations, Monetary Development, Prospects,", 1973 April 25; 26:08 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005791
    - 120. "Discount Rate, Current Boom, Future Prospects, Balance of Payments,", 1973 May 11; 26:08 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005792
    - 121. "Gold and the Dollar, Stock Market, Wage and Price Controls,", 1973 May 24; 23:07 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005793
    - 122. "Adam Smith, Controls, Dollar and Gold, Watergate and the Economy,", 1973 June 11; 25:35 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005794
    - 123. "Freeze, Dividend Limitation, Monetary Policy,", 1973 June 23; 29:29 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005795
    - 124. "The German Mark, Federal Reserve Action, Interest Rates, Subscribers' Queries,", 1973 July 4; 29:12 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005796
    - 125. "Phase Four, Monetary Developments, Interest Rates, Foreign Exchange,", 1973 July 18; 30:37 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005797
    - 126. "Fed's Talk And Action, Future Monetary Policy, International Monetary Situation,", 1973 August 2; 32:49 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005798